question_data = [
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming"
                     " pools and drinking water.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "The Sun rises from the North.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                           "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
                                           "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"
                                                                                                                ]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                           "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress"
                                                       " partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.",
                                           "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Jingle Bells was originally meant for Thanksgiving", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
